Guide to the Mark Hall Amitin/ World of Culture for the Performing Arts, Inc. Archive MSS.121
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Personal Papers
  - Subseries C: Albee Directs Albee
    - Contracts and correspondence: Kennedy Center., 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Contracts and correspondence: Korea 1979. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Contracts and correspondence: Manila, The Philippines., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Contracts and correspondence: Paramount Arts Center, IL., 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Contracts and correspondence: Venezuela., 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Actors' Equity., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040618004
    - Correspondence: Amitin, Albee, and their offices, August 31, 1977 - May 24, 1979., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: foreign sponsors, I.C.A., U.S. State Dept., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: institutions re: unbooked engagements 1977-1978. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: institutions re: unbooked engagements., 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: institutions re: unbooked engagements., 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: institutions re: unbooked engagements., 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: institutions re: unbooked engagements., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: institutions re: unbooked engagements., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and administration., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, performance dates, administration., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Financial., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Financial and booking., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Financial and booking., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Flyers (Hong Kong), playbill (Seoul), name plates in Chinese., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Leon Fried (assistant to Mark Amitin)., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - General administration., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Interview sheets, actors' photos, resumes., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Interview sheets, actors' photos, resumes., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Interview sheets, actors' photos resumes., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617212
    - Interview sheets, actors' photos, resumes., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Interview sheets, actors' photos, resumes., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Job applicants., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Letters to and from auditioned actors., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Lighting focus sheets., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Mailgrams to cast and crew announcing closing and reopening of show, October - November 1978. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Mark Hall Amitin Presents Inc., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Measurements for actors' costumes., undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Narrative - inception of Albee Directs Albee (3 typed pages)., undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Playbills., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Playbills., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Playbills - originals., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Stephen Pollock's (lighting designer) handwritten notes., undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Press releases, reviews., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Program information., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Publicity, touring information., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Résumés - Karl Eigsti, Stephen Pollock., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Sandbox musical score - William Flanagan., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Seals Theatre Company., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Substitution notices., undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Technical (drawings, plans, notes)., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Technical (drawings, plans, notes)., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Touring notes, telegrams, general administration., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Travel information., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - University of California poster for Box and Quotations., undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Various items - handwritten rehearsal schedule, tickets, flyers, booking calendar., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Subseries D: Scripts and Screenplays. These are organized alphabetically by writer.
    - Jean Anouilh, Antigone., undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617220
    - Stephan Balint, L-Train to Eldorado., undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Bandstand., undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ronald Bass, Sleeping with the Enemy, December 15, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Allan Bates, The Yellow Heat., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Saul Bellow, Seize the Day, July 17, 1985. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Andrew Bergman, The Freshman, January 1, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Adam Bernstein, The Beast Within., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Josef Bogdanovich, Cannibal in Manhattan., undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Lemuel Borden, Duse, Duncan and Craig, August 1, 1985. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Tia Brelis, The Mommy Market, July 7, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Jimmy Breslin, The Queen of the Leaky and Roof Circuit, February 1, 1988. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Leon Capetanos, Paul Mazursky, Moon Over Parador, March 9, 1987. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Jim Cash, Jack Epps, The Secret of My Success, May 12, 1986. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Matthew Chapman, Heart of Midnight, August 17, 1987. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Joel Coen, Ethan Coen, Miller's Crossing., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Jerome Coopersmith, Spenser for Hire, September 25, 1987. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - James Costigan, Theophilus North., undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Larry David, Jerry Seinfeld, Stand Up, March 24, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - James Dearden, A Kiss Before Dying, September 7, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Sean Delgado, Peggy Bruen, Alexa., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Pat Densham, Prince of Thieves., undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Tom DiCicillo, Box of Moonlight, April 1992. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Ray Dobbins, Colonial Boy., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Rosalyn Drexler, The Bed Was Full., undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Rosalyn Drexler, The Ice Queen., undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Lee Drysdale, Sweet Nothing., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - T.S. Eliot, Murder in the Cathedral., undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Todd Feuer, Hmmmmm?, October 12, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Jeffrey Fiskin, Revenge, March 4, 1988. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Robert Foster, Clinton and Nadine, October 8, 1987. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Brad Fraser, Unidentified Human Remains, undated and the True Nature of Human Love, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617238
    - Lowell Ganz, Babaloo Mandel, Vibes, November 7, 1986. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Jean Genet, The Balcony Trans. Jean-Claude van Itallie., undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Herb Gardner, The Goodbye People., undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gilbert Girion, Fakebook., undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Menahem Golan, A Great Wind Cometh, June 18, 1987. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - David Gordon, The Mysteries and What's so Funny, August 19, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Edward Gorsuch, Headshot, January 28, 1999. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Todd Graff, Used People, March 15, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Damian Gray, The Florentines, June 1989. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Maggie Greenwald, The Ballad of Little Joe, March 17, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bruce Harmon, Off Limits, October 5, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bruce Harmon, Reaching Out, December 14, 1989. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Amy Heckerling, Rat Race, December 7, 1940. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Beth Henley, The Miss Firecracker Contest., undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Klaus Hoch-Gunn, Even Vampires Get the Blues., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Keith Huff, Mud People, August 15, 1989. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - I Heard the Mermaids Singing, January 1987. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Jim Jarmusch, One Night in Memphis., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Len Jenkin, American Notes, September 16, 1985. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Ernest Joselovitz, Romance., undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Dusty Kay, Mick and Frankie, November 18, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - William Kennedy, Ironweed, October 25, 1985. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Larry Ketron, Fresh Horses, April 13, 1987. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Peter Lance, Miami Vice, January 7, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Mark Jordan Legan, I Burned Cody and on Monday., undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617246
    - James Lemmo, Randy Jurgenson, Heart., 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Ira Levin, Sliver, August 1992. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Romulus Linney, April Snow., undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Jon Lipsky, Steven Wang, Class., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Craig Lucas, Longtime Companion., 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bruce Lyons, Kely Lyons, The Mystery Of Pilau., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Michael McDowell, George H. Romero, Tales From the Darkside: The Movie., 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Ian McEwan, The Good Son, July 29, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Dennis McIntyre, State of Grace, April 10, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Steve McLean, Postcards From America, October 1992. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Keith McNally, Face of the Deep, July 1989. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Jacklyn Maddux, Maggie's Seein' Wonderful Things., 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Mark Magill, On the Trail of the Lonesome Pine, November 1, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - David Mamet, Glengarry Glen Ross, August 5, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - John Mankiewicz, Daniel Pyne, The Street, December 11, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Michael Mann, Miami Vice, March 28, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Bob Merrill, Hannah, February 1990. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Joseph Minion, Vampire's Kiss., undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Christopher Monger, Waiting for the Light., 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Richard Monka, Abbey Inc., August 31, 1996. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Alan Moskwoitz, Miami Vice, June 12, 1986. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Desmond Nakano, Last Exit to Brooklyn., undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617253
    - Desmond Nakano, Last Exit to Brooklyn., undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Never Waiver., undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Peter Noah, Cafe Americain, September 8, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Michael Paseornak, Cyberstorm., undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Walter W. Pitt, Bill Tunnicliffe, Deception, November 15, 1989. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Reinaldo Povod, La Puta Vida., undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - R.J., Fat Man and Little Boy, February 4, 1988. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Doug Richardson, Honor Bright, December 3, 1987. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Tim Robbins, Times are Changing Back, July 1991. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Alexandre Rockwell, Sollace Mitchell, In the Soup, January 28, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - David O. Russell, Swelter, April 21, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Kate Moira Ryan, Rescuing Marilyn., undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Nicholas St. John, China Girl, September 8, 1986. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Eric Sakolsky, The Body(typed MS with handwritten notes), July 1984. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Ken Selden, White Lies, August 1, 1991., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - William Shakespeare, As You Like It., undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - William Shakespeare, Macbeth., undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - William Shakespeare, Twelfth Night., undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Robin Shamburg, Adam Bernstein, Robert Breslo, Cash and Prizes, September 22, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - George Bernard Shaw, Androcles and the Lion., undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Isaiah Sheffer, Red Apple Best, February 1989. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - David Sheffield, Barry Blaustein, Coming to America., undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ron Shelton, Blaze, January 4, 1989. (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Michael Shurtleff, Up to Snuff., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Neil Simon, Broadway Bound., undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617261
    - Jane Spencer, Jon Zeiderman, Little Noises., undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Gudmundar Steinsson, Lukas., undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Tommy Swerdlow, Michael Goldberg, Blue Maaga, September 10, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Meg Switzgable, Passing Through Linden., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Ted Tally, White Palace, February 16, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Michael Tolkin, The New Age, July 14, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified scripts., undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Paul Valery, My Faust., undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Jean-Claude van Itallie, Ancient Boys., undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Jean-Calude van Itallie, The Master and Margarita., undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Jean-Claude van Itallie, Paradise Ghetto., undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Jean-Claude van Itallie, A Question of Love., undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Jean-Claude van Itallie, 3 Lives for Mississippi., undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Wisner Washam, All My Children., undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Gina Wendkos, Dinosaurs., 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Don Wigutow, Nightlife, February 1, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Larry Wilson, Caroline Thompson, The Addams Family., undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Susan Wittenberg, Carol Stein, Insomnia., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Doug Wright, Buzzsaw Berkeley., 1989 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Cao Yu, Peking Man., undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Steven Zaillian, Awakenings, April 6, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Steven Zaillian, Searching for Bobby Fischer, December 1, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Subseries E: Playbills, Programs, Flyers, Brochures.
    - The Actors Collective - The Dykes at Dunkirk, 1985. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617279
    - ACTAA 81, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Adam and the Experts (Nicholas Deutsch)., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Affiliate Artists News, Winter 1979. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Agnes of God (Michael Lindsay-Hogg)., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Albee Directs Albee., 1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Edward Albee biography., undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Alien Comic's Christmas in Outer Space, December 18, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Alien Comic's Night of Scary Comedy, October 26, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Allegro, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - All in Good Time, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - All's Well that Ends Well (Richard Jones)., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - All's Well that Ends Well (Trevor Nunn)., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Almost September (Richard Schechner), February 22, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Amadeus (Peter Hall), April 1981. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - American Ballet Theatre, May 1983. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - American Buffalo (Arvin Brown)., undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - American Center, Paris 1981. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - American College Theatre Festival., undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - American Notes (JoAnne Akalaitis), February 1988. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - American Silents., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - American Theatre Association Annual Convention., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Mark Amitin lectures and workshops., undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Ancient Boys (Gregory Keller)., undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - And Baby Makes Seven (Calvin Skaggs), May 1993. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Andorra (Anthony Torn)., undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Jo Andres., undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Angels in America (George C. Wolfe), July 1993. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Angels of Light, April 22, 1981. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Anna the Gypsy Swede (Viveca Lindfors)., 1992 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Another Person is a Foreign Country (Anne Bogart)., undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Anti-Clock., undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Antigone (Joseph Chaikin)., undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - APA-Phoenix., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - The Apple Tree (Mike Nichols), Aug 1967. (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - April is the Cruelest Month (Jospeh Siravo), April 1992. (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - The Arizona Project., undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Artists' Choice Series at MOMA., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Asian American International Film Festival., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - "Assault on the Arts: Culture and Politics in Nazi Germany"., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - The Astrakhan Coat (Donald McWhinnie), January 1967. (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - ATHEnews., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - The Bacchae (Michael Cacoyannis), September 1980. (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - The Balcony (Geoffrey Sherman), March 29, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - The Ballad of the Sad Cafe (R. Stuart White)., 1977 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Ballet Nationale de Marseilles., undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - The Baltimore Waltz (Stan Wojewodski)., undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - BAMazine, Fall 1997. (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Batsheva Dance Company., undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Bay Street Theatre Festival., undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - The Beauty Queen of Leenane (Garry Hynes), November 1998. (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Steven Ben Israel., undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Bent(Robert Allan Ackerman), 1980. (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Keith Berger., undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - The Bessies., undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - The Best American Short Play Reading Series., undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Better People(Karen Malpede)., undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Big River., undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Big Shot(Jack Gelber)., undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Biloxi Blues (Gene Saks)., undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Black Comedy (John Dexter), June 1967. (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Blood Red Roses (Alan Schneider)., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Bloolips., undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Books and Art in the USSR., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Booth (David Schweizer), January 1994. (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Bread and Puppet Theatre, undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Breaking the Code (Clifford Williams), April 1988. (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Brechtspiel (David Schechter)., undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Brighton Beach Memoirs (Gene Saks)., Apr 1983 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Broadway Bound (Gene Saks)., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music., undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Buried Child (Robert Woodruff)., undated (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Burn This (Marshall W. Mason)., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Steve Buscemi, Various., undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Business Committee for the Arts., undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Butoh and Beyond (Jeff Janisheski)., undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Cactus Flower (Abe Burrows)., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - David Cale., undated (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Casting Society of America., Oct 25, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Cats., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - The Caucasian Chalk Circle (David Wheeler)., undated (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - The Cave (Steve Reich, Beryl Korot), October 1993. (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Center Stage, October 1990. (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - "Charlie" Comedy Awards, November 22, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Children of a Lesser God (Gordon Davidson), September 1980. (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - China Film Week., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Ping Chong., undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - The Chopin Playoffs (Steven Zuckerman), May 15, 1986. (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - A Chorus Line., 1977 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Cinema and Society: An Asian Trilogy., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - City Junket (Mac McGinnes)., undated (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - City of Angels (Michael Blakemore)., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - City Opera., undated (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Class Enemy (Tony Tanner)., undated (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Clemens Performing Arts Center., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Clothes for a Summer Hotel (Jose Quintero)., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Cloud 9 (Tommy Tune), undated (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - The Colossal Theatre Company and Post-Vanguard., undated (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Columbia: The Sound of the Seventies., undated (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Compagnie de Danse Eddy Toussaint., undated (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Composer's Ensemble Theatre., undated (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Court Art of Kraton from the Court of Yogyakarta., undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - The Cradle Will Rock (John Houseman)., undated (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Crazy for You, January 1995. (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Melvin Bernhardt), July 1982. (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Crystal Theatre., undated (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Cure for the Biting of a Madde Dogge (Rebecca Moore)., undated (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Cymbeline (JoAnne Akalaitis), May 23, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Dance Theatre of Harlem., undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Dance Theater Workshop., undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Dancin' (Bob Fosse)., 1979 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Danton's Death (CSC Rep)., undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Danton's Death (Louis Rackoff)., undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - A Day in the Death of Joe Egg (Michael Blakemore), March 1968. (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - The Dead (John Huston)., undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Death of a Salesman (Michael Rudman), September 24, 1984. (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - De La Guarda., undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - The Deputy (Herman Shumlin), November 1964. (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - The Desert Music (Steve Reich)., undated (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Developing Projects Theatre., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Dialog/Curious George (Christopher Knowles, Robert Wilson), June 1980. (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - The Diary of Anne Frank (Martin Fried)., undated (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - The Dining Room (David Trainer)., undated (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - Dixon Place Events, July 1992. (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - Doctor Faustus (Tribeca Lab and High Noon Productions)., undated (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - Dona Rosita: While She Waits (John Olon)., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - Dracula (Dennis Rosa), May 1978. (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - Dracula: The Vampire King (Ezra Stone)., undated (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Drama Desk Awards., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - Dreamgirls (Michael Bennett), July 1982. (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - The Dresser (Michael Elliott), March 1982. (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Early Warnings (Steven Kent), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Edinburgh International Festival 1970. (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Einstein on the Beach., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Elektra (Lydia Koniordou), September 28, 1996. (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Eleo Pomare Dance Company, November 1983. (Box 12, Folder 136)
    - The Elephant Man (Jack Hofsiss)., undated (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - Elysium Theater Company, December 1986. (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - The Emelin Theatre, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - John Emigh, undated (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Empires and Appetites (Theatre for the New City)., undated (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Endangered Species (Martha Clarke)., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - End of the Rainbow., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617287
    - En Garde Arts., undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ensemble Studio Theatre., undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Entertaining Mr Sloane (John Tillinger)., undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Equus (John Dexter)., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Eros (Maureen Fleming)., undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Eros-Thanatos (Maurice Bejart), May 1982. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Everybody Knows Your Name (John Albano)., undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Every Good Boy Deserves Favour (Tom Stoppard), August 1979. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Everything in the Garden (Peter Glenville)., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Evita (Harold Prince), August, 1981. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Lewis Falb., undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Falsettos (James Lapine)., undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Fanfare (NYC Ballet)., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - The Fantasticks, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Fata Morgana (The Talking Band)., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)